







Total Experience: 14 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Highest Degree: MCA[Computers]

Notice Period: 1 Month

Current Designation: PMO Executive

Current Company: ALROWAD IT Solutions

Current Location: ABU DHABI, UAE

Pref. Location: Dubai, United Kingdom (UK), United States

(US)

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Team Lead/Tech Lead

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

 $\label{thm:continuous} \textit{Key Skills: PMO Executive, Team Lead/Tech Lead, Program \textit{M} an agement, PMO Functions, Software \textit{M} and \textit{M} and \textit{M} are \textit{M} and \textit{M} and \textit{M} are \textit{M} and \textit{M} and \textit{M} are \textit{M} are \textit{M} and \textit{M} are \textit{M}$ 

Development, Stakeholder Management, Risk Identification, Performance Monitoring, Client Engagement, Net, Oracle

PL/SQL, Mainframes, COBOL, CICS, JCL, Oracle, DB2, Datacom, VSAM

Verified: Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Active: 21-Jan-21

Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

#### Summary

Performance-driven professional with over 14 years of rich & extensive experience in Strategic Project Life Cycle Management, Client Engagement and People Management across Retail, Healthcare & Supply Chain industries Forward-focused Project & Portfolio Manager with exposure in swiftly completing projects with competent cross-functional skills and ensuring on time deliverables within pre-set cost parameters; with proficiency in Agile & Waterfall Methodologies Proven success in taking independent ownership of all technical aspects of software development lifecycle Growth catalyst with impressive success in implementing new ERP systems and upgraded existing ones depending on project needs

Bagged Star Performer for Management and Technical Excellence, Movers and Shakers Award for the Year 2014 An ambassador of change with excellence in gathering and understanding requirements of clients & other multiple stakeholders (at strategic and tactical levels), followed by translation into function

### **Work Experience**

ALROWAD IT Solutions as PMO Executive
May 2010 to Till Date

May 2019 to Till Date

Renamed as "Dynamic Smart Solutions LLC" starting from 2020 It is a semi government organization which belongs to Mnistry of Interior, Abu Dhabi; wherein all projects being managed are related to different governmental departments

- SPI as Project Manager Oct 2009 to Jan 2017
- Perot Systems as Senior Software Engineer Jan 2009 to Sep 2009

^ Back to Top

## **Education**

UG: BCA (Computers) from Madurai Kamraj University College, Madurai in 2003

PG: MCA (Computers) from cms college of science and commerce in 2007

## **Important**

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

## IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Windows 7/XP/2000/98			
ZOS			
OS-390			
Oracle PL/SQL,.NET			
Mainframes			
Cobol			
CICS			
JCL			
.NET			
Oracle			
DB2			
DATACOM			
VSAM			
JIRA			
Microsoft Project			
BITOOLS			
SQL DEVELOPER			
TOAD			
ENDEAVOUR			
FILE-AID			
XPEDITER			
INTERSET			
CONTROL-M			

^ Back to Top

# Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Malayalam				
Kannada				

^ Back to Top

## **Affirmative Action**

# **Work Authorization**

Category: **General**Physically Challenged: **No** 

Job Type: Permanent
Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.